var htmlQuiz = [
    {   question: "Which element is used for an image?",   
        correctAnswer: "&lt;img&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;a&gt;", "&lt;div&gt;", "&lt;img&gt;", "&lt;p&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "which element is used for a link?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;a&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;p&gt;", "&lt;a&gt;", "&lt;link&gt;", "&lt;target&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "which element is used for a button?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;button&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;btn&gt;", "&lt;link&gt;", "&lt;button&gt;", "&lt;btn-default&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "which element is used for a name input?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;input&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;contact&gt;", "&lt;div&gt;", "&lt;name&gt;", "&lt;input&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "How should a .html file begin?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;!doctype html&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;!doctype html&gt;", "&lt;body&gt;", "&lt;html&gt;", "&lt;!html document&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "What application can be used to style HTML?",
        correctAnswer: "css",
        incorrectAnswers: ["css", "horseshoe", "firebase", "style.form"],
    },
    {   question: "What element is most commonly used?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;div&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;div&gt;", "&lt;attach&gt;", "&lt;nest&gt;", "&lt;file&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "What is not a commonly used element?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;dari&gt;n",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;a&gt;", "&lt;darin&gt;", "&lt;div&gt;", "&lt;p&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "What element is used to define javascript?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;script&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;reference&gt;", "&lt;style&gt;", "&lt;java&gt;", "&lt;script&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "What element is used to define css?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;style&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;style&gt;", "&lt;script&gt;", "&lt;link&gt;", "&lt;doc&gt;"],
    },   
];


var cssQuiz = [
    {   question: "Which is not a selector",
        correctAnswer: "image",
        incorrectAnswers: ["image", "class", "id", "tag"],
    },
    {   question: "where would you put the <style> in html?",
        correctAnswer: "&lt;head&gt;",
        incorrectAnswers: ["&lt;head&gt;", "&lt;body&gt;", " &lt;script&gt;", "&lt;dom&gt;"],
    },
    {   question: "what is the syntax for pseudo element",
        correctAnswer: "::",
        incorrectAnswers: ["::", ";;", "!", "??"],
    },
    {   question: "when would you use !important",
        correctAnswer: "only if you have to",
        incorrectAnswers: ["only if you have to", "each line", "important sections", "to make bold"],
    },
    {   question: "what is a good way to understand css?",
        correctAnswer: "box model",
        incorrectAnswers: ["box model", "read the api docs", "use bootstrap", "dont use css"],
    },
    {   question: "what is a way to size a font",
        correctAnswer: "em ",
        incorrectAnswers: ["big", "em", "lg", "er"],
    },
    {   question: "what best describes media query",
        correctAnswer: "responsive",
        incorrectAnswers: ["responsive", "local", "host", "background"],
    },
    {   question: "what does a css reset do",
        correctAnswer: "clears any predefined settings",
        incorrectAnswers: ["clears any predefined settings", "freshens it up", "closes the window", "sets font color"],
    },
    {   question: "which is a css preprocessor",
        correctAnswer: "LESS",
        incorrectAnswers: ["LESS", "MORE", "FEW", "HUGE"],
    },
    {   question: "CSS stands for",
        correctAnswer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
        incorrectAnswers: ["Cascading Style Sheets", "Cool StyleS", " Computer Style Sheet", "Cats Swim Swiftly"],
    },   
];

var javascriptQuiz = [
    {   question: "javascript-1",
        correctAnswer: "signal weak",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-2",
        correctAnswer: "signal good",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-3",
        correctAnswer: "stop transmitting",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-4",
        correctAnswer: "affirmative",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-5",
        correctAnswer: "verbal communication only",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-6",
        correctAnswer: "out of service",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-7",
        correctAnswer: "in service",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-9",
        correctAnswer: "repeat",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-9",
        correctAnswer: "negative",
    },
    {   question: "javascript-10",
        correctAnswer: "suspicious property",
    },   
];
